eugenoprea.com 2019-04-24

# Privacy Policy – Eugen Oprea

### **Privacy Policy – Your privacy is important to us**

Thank you for visiting our web site. This Privacy Policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

EugenOprea.com is committed to protecting your privacy. Any personal information obtained from you will be handled in accordance with EugenOprea.com’s Privacy Policy.

  *   **Collection of Information**

When you visit our website, Analytics software that we use may collect your information about IP address, device information including operating system, location, mobile network information and standard web log information, such as your browser type, traffic to and from our site and the pages you accessed on our website.

In the event of making a purchase we may collect personally identifiable information, like name, email addresses and purchase details provided by PayPal.

  *   **Cookie/Tracking Technology**

The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the site, understanding how visitors use the site and for Google Analytics. Cookies can also help customize the site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.

We use these technologies to recognize you as an EugenOprea.com customer, help prevent fraud and promote trust and safety.

  *   **Distribution of Information**

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.

  *  **Commitment to Data Security**

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees  have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

  *  **Privacy Contact Information**

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below by e-mail:  **support [at] eugenoprea  [dot] com**

Thank you for visiting our website! We will work continuously to earn your trust.
